区块链、加密货币、非同质化代币、去中心化、去中心化金融、去中心化自治组织
Blockchain, crypto currency, NFT, decentralization, DEFI, DAO
不管你问的是投资者、风险投资家还是技术爱好者，
Whether you ask investors or venture capitalists or technology enthusiasts,
在社交媒体上，网络被认为是科技的下一件大事。
on social media, web is supposed to be the next big thing for technology.
在未来，
And in the future,
你所做的一切，
everything you do,
从在网上发布内容到进行金融交易，都将转化为存储在区块链上的令牌。
from posting content on the Web to making a financial transaction will be turned into a token stored on the blockchain.
现在，取决于你是谁，你在哪里，你知道什么，
Now, depending on who you are and where you are and what you know,
这听起来可能很棒，也可能很可怕，或者只是很困惑，或者同时是以上所有的，
this may sound awesome or terrifying or just plain confusing or all of the above at the same time,
我们一起来理解一下。
so let's make sense of this together.
我花了很多时间研究去中心化区块链技术，
I've spent a lot of time researching decentralization blockchain technologies,
这个想法被称为网络三。
and this idea promoted as web three.
我把这门课写成了资料词典
And I've made this course as a dictionary of source
帮助理解支撑这一切的术语和技术。
to help make sense of the jargon and technologies underpinning all of this.
本课程分为两章
This course is split into two chapters.
第一章是对web三和下一代web概念的高层次解释。
The 1st chapter is a high level explanation of the idea refer to as web three and the next version of the Web.
第二章深入探讨了区块链技术的工作原理，
The 2nd chapter is a deep dive into how blockchain technology works,
以及与区块链相关的所有术语的含义。
and what all the terminology associated with blockchain means.
对原则有牢固的把握
Having a firm grasp of the principles
以及围绕区块链和Web三意识形态的实践
and practices around blockchain and Web three ideology
让你有能力就我们共同的未来进行有意义的对话，
gives you the power to have meaningful conversations about our shared future,
我是来帮你做好的
and I'm here to help you get it right.
让我们开始吧
So let's get cracking.